Jade Gleason

gjade4901@gmail.com 917-412-6272

Self motivated and passionate about selling and increasing product and market knowledge. Go getter with experience in value based selling and managing warm leads. Creative professional collaborating with team to build long lasting relationships with clients and retain existing clients.

Experience

Lendzi, New York City— Sales Development Representative

January 2022 - PRESENT

- Qualify buying interest for warm leads, 250-450 dials per day and 3-4 hours of talk time.
- Email, call and text to educate prospective customers and discover opportunities.
- Work with 5 assigned account executives to develop market strategy and manage sales pipeline, about 10-20 businesses funded monthly.
- Consistently achieve and exceed 11 approval quota set on weekly basis, highest approval rate was 26 and took 3 weeks to hit.
- Use internal relationships to exceed customer expectations and provide support to the team. Identify pain points and customer solutions.

Upwork, New York City — *Ghost Writer*

September 2017 - January 2018

- Conduct and create SEO and article content through sourcing and fact checking four 500 word non-fiction articles to meet clients' goals.
- Work with reviewer to target desired article outcome through feedback while revising and editing independently with turnaround deadlines.

Thomas Edison Papers, New Brunswick, NJ — Administrative Assistant

September 2014 - May 2018

• Organize, monitor, and prioritize up to date files using Microsoft Excel and Access sheets timely and efficiently for internal teams to review and revise for educational resources.

Good Journey, New York City — Writer Internship

June 2017 - August 2017

- Create, write, and pitch story topics and manage website's content.
- Build cross-functional relationships with brands and establish oneself as brand expert.

Education

Rutgers, New Brunswick, NJ — Bachelors in Journalism

January 2014 - May 2019

• Minors in English and Social Justice